export const questionData = [
  {
    qno:1,
    question: `CSS stands for `,
    op1:`a) Cascade style sheets`,
    op2:`b) Color and style sheets`,
    op3:`c) Cascading style sheets`,
    op4:`d) None of the above`,
    ans:`c)`
  },
  {
    qno:2,
    question: `Which of the following is the correct syntax for referring the external style sheet? `,
    op1:`a) <style src = example.css>`,
    op2:`b) <style src = "example.css" >`,
    op3:`c) <stylesheet> example.css </stylesheet>`,
    op4:`d) <link rel="stylesheet" type="text/css" href="example.css">`,
    ans:`d)`
  },
  {
    qno:3,
    question: `The property in CSS used to change the background color of an element is`,
    op1:`a) bgcolor`,
    op2:`b) color`,
    op3:`c) background-color`,
    op4:`d) All of the above`,
    ans:`c)`
  },
  {
    qno:4,
    question: `Which of the following is the correct syntax to display the hyperlinks without any underline?`,
    op1:`a) a {text-decoration : underline;}`,
    op2:`b) a {decoration : no-underline;}`,
    op3:`c) a {text-decoration : none;}`,
    op4:`d) None of the above`,
    ans:`c)`
  },
  {
    qno:5,
    question: `Which of the following property is used as the shorthand property for the padding properties?`,
    op1:`a) padding-left`,
    op2:`b) padding-right`,
    op3:`c) padding`,
    op4:`d) All of the above`,
    ans:`c)`
  },
  {
    qno:6,
    question: `Are the negative values allowed in padding property`,
    op1:`a) Yes`,
    op2:`b) No`,
    op3:`c) Can't say`,
    op4:`d) May be`,
    ans:`b)`
  },
  {
    qno:7,
    question: `The CSS property used to specify the transparency of an element is`,
    op1:`a) Opacity`,
    op2:`b) filter`,
    op3:`c) visibility`,
    op4:`d) overlay`,
    ans:`a)`
  },
  {
    qno:8,
    question: `The CSS property used to set the distance between the borders of the adjacent cells in the table is`,
    op1:`a) border-collapse`,
    op2:`b) border-radius`,
    op3:`c) border-spacing`,
    op4:`d) None of the above`,
    ans:`c)`
  },
  {
    qno:9,
    question: `In how many ways can CSS be written in?`,
    op1:`a) 1`,
    op2:`b) 2`,
    op3:`c) 3`,
    op4:`d) 4`,
    ans:`c)`
  },
  {
    qno:10,
    question: `How can we write comments in CSS?`,
    op1:`a) /* */`,
    op2:`b) //`,
    op3:`c) #`,
    op4:`d) All of the above`,
    ans:`a)`
  }
]
export default questionData;